Guide to the New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection OH.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Richard Walsh, November 4, 1987
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-496 - OH-01-497)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-483, Box 29, Audiocassette 149A - 149B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 149A - 149B)
- Angelina Wanderly, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Katherine Ward, April 24, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Keri Webster, April 17, 1991
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 37, Audiocassette 206)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 206)
- Philip Weightman, April 11, 1981
  AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education; Voting rights for African-Americans.
  - Transcript (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-345 - OH-01-347)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-345 - OH-01-347, Box 29, Audiocassette 133A - 133C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 133A - 133C)
- Grace Weiner, August 21, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Index (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-183)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-183)
  - Original Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 136)
- Louis Weinstock, December 16, 1980
  - Transcript (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Index (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-184 - OH-01-186)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-184 - OH-01-186)
  - Original Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 135A - 135B)
- Everett Wiltshire, November 12, 1996
  - Transcript (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Index (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-187 - OH-01-188)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-187 - OH-01-188, Box 34, Audiocassette 245A - 245B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 245A - 245B)
- Conrad Woelfel, March 27, 1980
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-189 - OH-01-190)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-189, Box 13, Cd OH-01-190, Box 29, Audiocassette 134A - 134B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 134A - 134B)
- Vincent Young, August 4, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 148A)
- Sol Zalon, May 29, 1980
  - Index (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-387 - OH-01-391)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-387 - OH-01-391)
  - Original Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 139A - 139C)
- Helen Zalph, September 6, 1981
  - Index (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-356)
  - Original Recordings (Box 38, Audiocassette 138)
- Irving Zeidman, February 14, 1985
  - Transcript (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-426 - OH-01-430)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-426 - OH-01-430)
  - Original Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 140A - 140C)
- Belle Zeller, January 8, January 9, and January 14, 1986
  Related Materials
  Zeller was interviewed by Irwin Yellowitz, a professor of labor history at the City University of New York and fellow Professional Staff Congress member. More information about Yellowitz and the Professional Staff Congress is available in the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Oral History Collection. These collections are also held by Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives; call number WAG 009 and OH 061 respectively.
  - Transcript (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-191 - OH-01-195)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-191 - OH-01-195)
  - Original Recordings (Box 30, Audiocassette 160A - 160C)